Nighttime and Idols
Hello everyone, this is Takaichi Ho. I am Tomoko Hazuki. I am Aoba Mori.
Yes, this time we are going to perform together in Tokyo Nighttime Land vol. 4,
Today, I would like to talk about our 3BJr. days.
We originally started a group called 3BJr. on November 1, 2014.
It has been exactly 9 years.
Yes, but our first stage performance was at Moiroku Burgett's Women's Festival 2014 on November 24, 2014.
It was exactly 9 years ago that I was allowed to perform as an opening artwork at the International Forum, a live viewing venue for men only, on November 24, 2014.
It was a huge stage, and I was so blessed to have such a big stage for the first time.
And we covered a Momokuro song at the International Forum, and I got to wear Momokuro's costume.
I got to wear a little of Momokuro's outfit, and I love Arline.
And I love Arline, and it was her costume.
I wore it while thinking about it, and it left a deep impression on me.
But it's been 9 years since then, isn't it fast? We have been active as 3B Junior for 4 years since then.
Were there any memorable moments?
There were so many, my memory is a little short, but we had so many lessons that I don't know how many times we met each week.
3B Junior had a lot of older and younger groups, but the one thing I do remember is that there were 26 of us, and we were all together in the mirror.
I remember that there were 26 of us, and when you have a lesson in front of a mirror with that many people, it's a big place, and it's not that I didn't notice, but when I started, I was probably in front of the others.
So I was always second or third from the front, so the sisters were always the first to see the money.
I'm always in the front row, and it's embarrassing.
I'm always in the front row, it's embarrassing... but it's like I'm fixed in a certain position, you know, and then I get to dance, and when the lesson comes, I'm right here.
I was at the very back, opposite end of the line from Tomo, who was probably at the very back. I have an image.
I was not good at dancing, and I was at the end of the line, thinking I couldn't dance anymore, and I was in the corner, like this, thinking I wasn't good at dancing either.
It was embarrassing. It was embarrassing.
You were involved with us then, too.
Mr. Kettle is here, so...
Oh, Mr. Kettle.
Actually, Mr. Kettle No. 3, No. 3?
No. 3?
I'm sorry, Mr. Kettle No. 3, right? I'm sorry, Mr. Kakan-kun III.
You're pushing yourself too hard, aren't you?
So I'd like to talk to him.
Do you remember Mr. Yakan?
He's been involved with you since 2016.
So, Mr. Takai and the others are going on a samurai training mission.
Mori-san and his group are going to do about 20 shows in December to complete 50 shows for the year.
Mr. Azuki and his group did a lot of street gigs and it was surprisingly cold...
I've seen a lot of things, so there it is.
Yes, there was! Yes, there was!
There was, wasn't there?
They were selling cassette tapes, and I'd never touched a set tape before.
I've never really touched a set tape, so I was thinking how nostalgic it was.
I've never touched a set tape before, so I was thinking how nostalgic it was, and I was thinking how good it was back in the day, and I was selling them.
Wow!
When we were going around shopping malls for free live shows together...
Is it really different from the street live performance? It's a little bit different.
It's a totally different kind of homey feeling.
I see.
Also, sometimes people who are just walking around will stay with us.
So you have a lot of freedom.
It's amazing.
I think it's the kindness that comes from the street live.
But I was thinking that the song that Leaf Citron was singing at the time was really suited to the homey atmosphere of the street live show.
Leaf Citron used to sing on a bench, so I wondered if he brought a bench to the street show.
I wondered if she would bring a bench to the street performance or not.
How are you going to do that?
You mean you're going to adopt it?
That's amazing.
And so on and so forth. And there were all kinds of things.
There was a time, wasn't there?
There was a time when we did an all-out live show on Christmas Day.
We did a one-day green
We did a 7-day show at the Green Club, and every day there was someone missing.
Every day there was a live performance by a group of three junior members, each of whom had a different unit, and we would show them which group was the best today.
I'll show you which group was the best today. I'll go to bed every night without getting into a battle.
Everyone wanted to win, so one group won, but there were no other groups, and it was definitely one of the newcomers.
And then, well, the high form was, you know, looking at the pictures, and at the end, everyone said, "It's going to open," instead of, "I'm not going.
There was also a group that my family was in called Honey Rocket, and Honey Rocket was a group that went to Rocca Japonica and then went on to train as a warrior.
We were sent off by everyone, and I don't know why, but there was a live concert on the day we were sent off.
I don't know why, but there was a flu pandemic... what did you go to?
There were 7 of us, but only 8 of us were allowed to go.
I'm sure the propolis of the rare raisers was not enough to meet the needs of the group.
I was showing them how to do it, when I got a call from someone saying, "Excuse me, I need a helper.
What? What 3b place on the skeet?
There are only two Honey Rocket members and we have too much information and we're going to have to leave at a moment's notice.
I said I didn't feel like we were being sent out, and there were 12 parts, but one of them left in May...
But one of the members left in May, so I was left on my own, and at the end I put everyone's face on two chapters, so now there were seven of us.
I was right... but I couldn't send them out like this... so I had to rearrange the chapters and do it another day.
I hope I caused you a lot of trouble.
I'm not going to be defeated by the lymph helmet.
There were many mysterious benefit events like the one where you lost if you let Blackbeard fly.
There was a game of catch, wasn't there?
If you could catch it, you could talk to them. You couldn't? They played some kind of history game.
Like some kind of history game where they play a song and you talk about the person who was sitting where you were sitting.
No, I understand that, but there was that too, the Prince Shotoku game.
There was a Prince Shotoku Taishi game, and there was a lot of people, so everyone was talking at the same time.
It's a bit chaotic, isn't it?
We do that, too. I do that kind of thing, though. Maybe you'll remember me better if you're the one who called me.
If you'd like to leave a voice comment, please do so.
It was there.
We might remember that more than you do. Please leave a voice line in the comments.
But... you've become a big sister over the years.
I wonder if you're used to it.
Mr. Ichikawa is the rain flash of yug Ichikawa-san, it was your birthday last time, and you're 20 years old!
Oh, really?
So, among the people who went to 3BJr. at that time, I can't drink yet, and at this point I can't drink.
Samiya Nakahara and Hana-chan are the only ones who can't drink at this point.
So we are all adults now, 24 of us.
I was so surprised when Yuzuki Ichikawa from Rainflash posted on her instagram that she turned 20, I commented that she was 20 and congratulated her and she replied.
And when I looked at the comment section, I saw that a lot of 3B members commented that Yuzu had already turned 20.
I thought everyone was feeling the same way.
The passage of time is scary, isn't it?
Because I had the impression that they were an elementary school team.
Yes, yes, we sang "Frozen Mandarin Oranges" together as a group of three elementary school students at that time.
You must be 20 years old now.
I'm not a little Yuzuki anymore... because I'm not a little Yuzuki anymore... because I'm an adult.
I'm going to be an adult Yuzuki
Yuzuki the older sister
I'm going to be a big sister Yuzuki.
Well, we're growing up too, so let's see how we've grown up again.
I hope we can show you our growth again.
I hope we can show you what we've grown up to be at the Tokyo Night Festival and so on.
I'll do my best!
I've been able to make it longer, haven't I?
Of course, I'm 22 years old.
Your pose is lame.
I'm 22 years old, and my pose is lame.I mean, the pose of the 22 on top is lame.
Yes, that's why we'll be bringing you the bottom with these three as well.
So far my partners were Aoba Mori, Ho Koichi and Tomoko Hazuki!
Bye bye!